good morning RBX Rob viewers we are
going to be trying something new as
usual I can't promise anything until
I've done it for a while but I'm going
to try so I've got my coffee in honor of
coffee boost time so 9 a.m. my time
wherever I am now right now I'm in North
Carolina but that's going to change in
July looks like I'll be all over the
country um traveling across the country
so stay tuned for that um and
hypothetically we'll be doing some some
coffee talk with people from those areas
so I'm looking forward to meeting people
uh all over the world as well well
starting with America how about
that so if you want to come I look I
have always wanted to be if you can't
tell I grew up and in fact we did a
really fun thing this morning about it I
grew up listening to 80s music with Five
Sisters shellacking our bathroom walls
with hairspray and listening to 80s
music and it was a really great time you
know to work on my really finely crafted
mullet BOS lurman says don't mess with
your too your hair too much when you're
younger you'll it'll all go away guess
what it went away but it was nice while
I had it while I had it you know I
remember Karen Petty playing with my
hair in seminary uh while and she was
like it was nice it was point
is I do like to get silly I like to
listen to great music in the morning and
I like to drink coffee and by the way
that's a really great time to answer
questions um in kind of a low stress
environment if you want a consistent
time to find me I know it's hard 9 isn't
it 10:41 I know this is a video I'm
making a video right now because I was
waiting for you guys to come in we're
going to do co-working right now so
immediately after that coffee coffee
boost time in the morning at 9:00 a.m.
my time that's what I'm trying to do um
I will be doing other things um most
likely I'll be doing co-working
uh streams I can't always promise we're
going to have music coworking streams we
talked about that I did another video
about that um but like when like today
when I can do something with the
community together while we're doing
research or or working at a problem or
something like that that I can then work
and I'm actually got my work computer on
right now then we'll go ahead and we'll
do that as well but if you want to tune
in for the absolute crazy morning DJ
Vibe where I just let it all go and I
say things like You're listening to RBX
Rob on
twitch.tv I love saying that and I get
to use all my special effects
welcome yeah or I can say you know I can
say that's the monster truck rally one
we say welcome Bellum I can have all
this fun thing it's it's another phase
it is definitely another phase um yeah
and um the one of the reasons that I'm
adding this by the way is I just told
everybody that I'm not going to be doing
the you know 8 hour co-working with
music on Stream So I at least want to uh
an opportunity to touch base with
everybody get excited for the day not
really have an agenda maybe talk about
the latest news uh like Scarlet
Johansson I wish she would register her
voice to Sky but she won't and she
shouldn't for free you know crazy things
like that the really cringey stuff that
you get from a morning DJ so if you want
that I don't care where I am I am going
to so help me Rob I'm going to try how
about
that I'm going to try to be up and be
here at 9:00 a.m. yeah yeah I know it's
hard for me everybody else has to be at
work by 9:00 a.m. and and and I'm having
a hard time even like consistently live
streaming from my room where the bed is
right
there so we're going to go ahead and do
that um again we're doing GitHub actions
right now so I'm going to turn into that
but I just want to make a quick uh video
for you just to let you know cuz I
really want to invite my community to
come on in and feel like they can get a
good start to the day or they can touch
base with the rest of us and I was
really sad about moving losing that
connection um you know kind on kind of a
daily consistent time sometimes like
when I go Mountain Biking For example
like yesterday when we were gravel
biking on the mountain bike trails I
couldn't really watch the chat very well
because because you know I I couldn't I
couldn't interact with the chat but but
during coffee time coffee boost time I
definitely can I can definitely read all
the chat I can get to know you um if
you're new I can you know find out where
you're from it's something that I have
always wanted to try to do on this
stream is to actually get to know the
people in my community I know it's crazy
this is probably why I'll never be
really super big but the people who are
here I tend to try to you know remember
you as much as my old brain can so come
join us come join our fam as as a few
people been saying and I'm I'm okay with
that slang by the way when I first heard
the term slang fam I was like you're not
really my family why are you say I get
it I get it know let's go fam let's go
artti big fam come on in for coffee talk
and coffee boost time we'll see you
tomorrow morning at 9:00 a.m.